Guide to The Women's Sports Foundation Records 1950-2019 (bulk, 1974-2018) MS 3199
New-York Historical Society
- Series III. Staff records, 1974-2014; 30 Linear feet in 30 record cartons
  - Subseries III.E. Chief Financial Officer records, 1974-2014; 13 Linear feet in 13 record cartons
    - Investment info ML, 2004-2008 (Offsite-box 72, Folder 17)
    - [Insurance policies] (2 folders), 2014 (Offsite-box 72, Folder 18-19)
    - Insurance, 2013 (Offsite-box 72, Folder 20)
    - Certificate of Incorporation copies, 1990-2011 (Offsite-box 72, Folder 21)
    - Current general insurance (2 folders), 2013 (Offsite-box 72, Folder 22-23)
    - Policy correspondence, 2008-2012 (Offsite-box 72, Folder 24)
    - Insurance (2 folders), 2010-2011 (Offsite-box 73, Folder 1-2)
    - Insurance - general (6 folders), 2006-2010 (Offsite-box 73, Folder 3-8)
    - Marsh/ to be filed, 1998, 2006 (Offsite-box 73, Folder 9)
    - Mutual of America information and 5500 tax forms (15 of 36 folders), 1995-2003 (Offsite-box 73, Folder 10-24)
    - Mutual of America information and 5500 tax forms (21 of 36 folders), 2004-2016 (Offsite-box 74, Folder 1-21)
    - Audit committee meeting notes, 2010-2011 (Offsite-box 74, Folder 22)
    - Functional expenses, 2010 (Offsite-box 74, Folder 23)
    - Year end, 2010 (Offsite-box 74, Folder 24)
    - Audit/ 990, 2009-2010 (Offsite-box 74, Folder 25)
    - Joint costs, 2009 (Offsite-box 74, Folder 26)
    - Functional expenses, 2009 (Offsite-box 74, Folder 27)
    - Year end (2 of 3 folders), 2009 (Offsite-box 74, Folder 28-29)
    - Year end (1 of 3 folders), 2009 (Offsite-box 75, Folder 1)
    - Joint cost allocation, 2008-2009 (Offsite-box 75, Folder 2)
    - Functional expenses, 2008 (Offsite-box 75, Folder 3)
    - Year end (2 folders), 2008 (Offsite-box 75, Folder 4-5)
    - Audit RFP, 2009 (Offsite-box 75, Folder 6)
    - Audit RFP (2 folders), 2007 (Offsite-box 75, Folder 7-8)
    - Audit RFP responses (2 folders), 2006-2007 (Offsite-box 75, Folder 9-10)
    - [Financial statements and reports] (7 of 12 folders), 2003-2015 (Offsite-box 75, Folder 11-17)
    - [Financial statements and reports] (5 of 12 folders), 1994-2002 (Offsite-box 76, Folder 1-5)
    - Form 990 filing (17 folders), 1994-2015 (Offsite-box 76, Folder 6-22)
    - Sports Museum (1 of 2). 5 folders, 2003-2011 (Offsite-box 77, Folder 1-5)
    - Sports Museum (2 of 2). Digital files, 2003 (Digital folder MS3199, Folder Box77_F5)
      Contains digital files originally stored on CD in Box 77 Folder 5. Files include PDF files, GIF image files, and HTML files. Contents include correspondence, logo images, and HTML websites related to the Sports Museum.
    - BJK Center (2 folders), 2008-2009 (Offsite-box 77, Folder 6-7)
    - Finance Committee meetings (2 folders), 2007 January-February (Offsite-box 77, Folder 8-9)
    - Finance Committee miscellaneous, 2001-2009 (Offsite-box 77, Folder 10)
    - Investment meeting, 2007 March 5 (Offsite-box 77, Folder 11)
    - Finance Committee meeting, 2007 January 22 (Offsite-box 77, Folder 12)
    - Executive Committee meetings, 2006-2007 (Offsite-box 77, Folder 13)
    - Finance Committee (4 folders), 2007 May-2008 June (Offsite-box 77, Folder 14-17)
    - Audit Committee meeting (2 folders), 2005-2007 (Offsite-box 77, Folder 18-19)
    - Finance Committee (3 of 14 folders), 2006 January-March (Offsite-box 77, Folder 20-22)
    - Finance Committee (11 of 14 folders), 2005 June-December, 2006 October-December (Offsite-box 78, Folder 1-11)
    - Investment Committee, 2006 September 29 (Offsite-box 78, Folder 12)
    - Finance Committee, 2006 August 29 (Offsite-box 78, Folder 13)
    - Audit Committee, 2009 April (Offsite-box 78, Folder 14)
    - Audit Committee, 2008 April (Offsite-box 78, Folder 15)
    - Ethics Committee, 2005-2007 (Offsite-box 78, Folder 16)
    - Investment Committee, 2005-2007 (Offsite-box 78, Folder 17)
    - Trustee meetings (7 folders), 2010-2012 (Offsite-box 78, Folder 18-24)
    - Planning meeting, 2010 August 9 (Offsite-box 78, Folder 25)
    - Executive Committee meetings, 2010-2011 (Offsite-box 78, Folder 26)
    - Board prep, 2011 (Offsite-box 78, Folder 27)
    - Trustee meetings (5 of 8 folders), 2008 December-2010 June (Offsite-box 78, Folder 28-32)
    - Trustee meetings (3 of 8 folders) (Offsite-box 79, Folder 1-3)
    - Staff - general meetings, 2006-2011 (Offsite-box 78, Folder 4)
    - Ops staff meeting, 2007-2010 (Offsite-box 78, Folder 5)
    - Carmelina, 2006-2007 (Offsite-box 78, Folder 6)
    - Information systems, 2009-2010 (Offsite-box 78, Folder 7)
    - Steve, 2006-2007 (Offsite-box 78, Folder 8)
    - Senior staff (1 of 2). 6 folders, 2005-2010 (Offsite-box 79, Folder 9-14)
    - Senior staff (2 of 2). Digital files, 2006 (Digital folder MS3199, Folder Box79_F13)
      Contains digital files originally stored on CD in Box 79 Folder 15. Files are arranged in two general folders labelled "Linda_Docs" and "Barry_Docs" and contain a variety of file formats generated and accessed by the staff in the course of their work. Formats include PDF files, Microsoft Word files, and Microsoft Excel files. File contents include correspondence, sample letters, financial and budget documentation and planning, schedules, and meeting minutes.
    - Aspire Higher search, 1988 (Offsite-box 79, Folder 15)
    - WSF Annual reports, 2000, 2002-2003 (Offsite-box 79, Folder 16)
    - The Decade in Decline: Gender Equity in High School Sports research report, 2012 October (Offsite-box 79, Folder 17)
    - Women in the 2000, 2004 and 2008 Olympic and Paralympic Games report, 2009 September (Offsite-box 79, Folder 18)
    - GoGirlGo! strategic plan, 2004 (Offsite-box 79, Folder 19)
    - The Billies programs, 2006, 2008 (Offsite-box 79, Folder 20)
    - Annual Salute to Women in Sports programs, 2007-2011 (Offsite-box 79, Folder 21)
    - WSF Guide to Planned Giving, circa 2005 (Offsite-box 79, Folder 22)
    - WSF holiday card, circa 2005 (Offsite-box 79, Folder 23)
    - Beverly Wiltshire event invitation, 2011 November 9 (Offsite-box 79, Folder 24)
    - Financial statements and auditors' report, 2010-2011 (Offsite-box 79, Folder 25)
    - Financial statements and auditors' report (3 folders), 2011-2012 (Offsite-box 80, Folder 1-3)
    - Annual audit presentation, 2013 April (Offsite-box 80, Folder 4)
    - Database reports [disassembled binder], 2002 (Offsite-box 80, Folder 5)
    - Standard response binder [disassembled binder], 1996-1998 (Offsite-box 80, Folder 6)
    - Donor relations playbook [disassembled binder], 2006 (Offsite-box 80, Folder 7)
    - Employee handbook [disassembled binder], 2007-2012 (Offsite-box 80, Folder 8)
    - Strategic planning committee meeting materials [disassembled binder], 2001 April 11 (Offsite-box 80, Folder 9)
    - WSF annual reports [disassembled binder], 1982-2001 (Offsite-box 80, Folder 10)
    - WSF physical inventory [disassembled binder] (2 folders), 2002 December (Offsite-box 80, Folder 11-12)
    - The New Agenda: a blueprint for the future of women's sports [disassembled binder] (4 folders), 1983 (Offsite-box 80, Folder 13-16)
    - Annual Salute to Women in Sports silent auction, 2012 (Offsite-box 80, Folder 17)
    - Development team playbook [disassembled binder] (2 folders), circa 2001 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 1-2)
    - NYAD notebook [disassembled binder] (2 folders), 2011 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 3-4)
    - Financial statements and auditors' report (3 folders), 2012-2013 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 5-7)
    - WSF annual reports (2 folders), 1993-2005 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 8-9)
    - Annual Salute to Women in Sports programs (2 folders), 1996-2000, 2002 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 10-11)
    - Invoices, 2011-2012 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 12)
    - Planned giving request, 2002-2005 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 13)
    - American Quarter Horse Association National Female Equestrian Award, 1999-2010 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 14)
    - Carol Mann Grants for Girls Golf Fund, 2000-2010 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 15)
    - Deborah Slaner Larkin Advocacy Fund, 2000-2010 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 16)
    - Linda Riddle/SGMA Endowed Scholarship, 1992-2012 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 17)
    - Dr. Donna A. Lopiano Leadership Fund, 2008-2010 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 18)
    - Dorothy G. Blaney/Billie Jean King Internship, 2008-2010 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 19)
    - Ford Motor Company Jump Start Grant, 2008-2010 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 20)
    - Jennifer Leeds Moms Dads & Daughters in Sports Fund, 2000-2010 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 21)
    - Katie & Perrie Fund, 1997-2010 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 22)
    - Darlene A. Kluka Women's Sports & Physical Activity Research Fund, 2000-2010 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 23)
    - Lilo Leeds Women's Sports & Fitness Participation Research Endowment, 1999-2010 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 24)
    - Lissa McLean/Tuti Scott Internship Fund, 2003-2010 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 25)
    - SportsMatters Grants for Girls Program, 2001-2010 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 26)
    - Susan Wellington Grant, 2011 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 27)
    - Janet T. Swanson Fund, 2000-2010 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 28)
    - Eliminate Homophobia in Sport Educational Fund, 2004-2010 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 29)
    - Robin Roberts GoGirlGo! Fund, 2007-2010 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 30)
    - Rusty Kanokogi Fund for the Advancement of U.S. Judo, 2009-2010 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 31)
    - RYKA Women's Fitness Grant, 2002-2010 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 32)
    - Vishay/Zandman Endowed Grant, 1997-2010 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 33)
    - Women's Sports Foundation Endowment, 2008-2009 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 34)
    - Sample donor letter, 2007 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 35)
    - Dorothy Harris Endowed Fund, 1990-2009 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 36)
    - Long Island Grants for Girls Endowment, 1997-2009 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 37)
    - Endowed fund agreements, 1992-2009 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 38)
    - Inactive funds, 1997-2004 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 39)
    - Misc. [planned giving checklists], 2010 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 40)
    - NYAD (3 folders), 2014 (Offsite-box 82, Folder 1-3)
    - Alphabetical donor files (15 folders), 1986-2011 (Offsite-box 82, Folder 4-18)
      Contains individual donor files in alphabetical order.
- Series IV. Departmental records, 1971-2018; 146 Linear feet in 146 record cartons
  Arranged in 8 subseries:
  Subseries IV.A. "Foundation files"
  Subseries IV.B. Advocacy records
  Subseries IV.C. Research records
  Subseries IV.D. Education records
  Subseries IV.E. Events and development records
  Subseries IV.F. Community impact records
  Subseries IV.G. Marketing and partnerships records
  Subseries IV.H. Operations and finance records
  - Subseries IV.A. "Foundation files", 1992-2012; 5.5 Linear feet in 5.5 record cartons
    Subseries IV.A contains a group of records labeled in the WSF offices as "Foundation Files." These folders contain grant proposals, donation request letters, applications, correspondence, and major giving routing forms related to individual foundations, corporations, and federal programs. Material dates from 1992-2012.
    The files were maintained in original order as removed from filing cabinets labeled "Foundation Files." A core range of alphabetical files is followed by individual folders.
    - Family Foundations - Misc. (re: individuals), 2010 (Offsite-box 82, Folder 19)
    - Misc. Foundations, 2006 (Offsite-box 82, Folder 20)
    - Alphabetical files: A (18 of 27 folders), 2003-2012 (Offsite-box 82, Folder 21-38)
    - A (9 of 27 folders), 2003-2012 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 1-9)
    - B (20 folders), 1998-2012 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 10-29)
    - C (9 of 30 folders), 1999-2012 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 30-38)
    - C (21 of 30 folders), 1999-2012 (Offsite-box 84, Folder 1-21)
    - D (9 folders), 2000-2012 (Offsite-box 84, Folder 22-30)
    - F (10 folders), 1999-2012 (Offsite-box 84, Folder 31-40)
    - G (9 folders), 2000-2012 (Offsite-box 84, Folder 41-49)
    - H-I (2 of 23 folders), 2001-2012 (Offsite-box 84, Folder 50-51)
    - H-I (21 of 23 folders), 2001-2012 (Offsite-box 85, Folder 1-21)
    - J (13 folders), 1999-2012 (Offsite-box 85, Folder 22-34)
    - K (8 folders), 1999-2010 (Offsite-box 86, Folder 1-8)
    - L (11 folders), 1997-2011 (Offsite-box 86, Folder 9-19)
    - M (13 folders), 1995-2012 (Offsite-box 86, Folder 20-32)
    - N-O (16 folders), 1998-2012 (Offsite-box 86, Folder 33-48)
    - P-Q (13 folders), 1992-2012 (Offsite-box 87, Folder 1-13)
    - R (10 of 16 folders), 1998-2012 (Offsite-box 87, Folder 14-23)
    - R (6 of 16 folders), 1998-2012 (Offsite-box 88, Folder 1-6)
    - S (29 folders), 1992-2012 (Offsite-box 88, Folder 7-35)
    - T (7 folders), 1997-2011 (Offsite-box 88, Folder 36-42)
    - U-V (10 folders), 1998-2012 (Offsite-box 88, Folder 43-52)
    - W-Z (2 of 22 folders), 2003-2012 (Offsite-box 88, Folder 53-54)
    - W-Z (20 of 22 folders), 2003-2012 (Offsite-box 89, Folder 1-20)
    - National Women's Health Week - RFPS 2011 + OWN/Conf, 2011-2012 (Offsite-box 89, Folder 21)
    - State Dept-ECA Information/Backup: Empowering Women and Girls Through Sport (6 folders), 2011-2012 (Offsite-box 89, Folder 22-27)
    - FY - NY App OJJDP, 2010-2012 (Offsite-box 89, Folder 28)
    - Atlanta App OJJDP, 2010-2011 (Offsite-box 89, Folder 29)
    - DCTAT Instruction Manual, 2009-2011 (Offsite-box 89, Folder 30)
    - Corporation for National and Community Service (CNCS) Capacity Building, 2011 (Offsite-box 89, Folder 31)
    - HHS - Prep (Marc Clark), 2010-2011 (Offsite-box 89, Folder 32)
    - HHS - Community Transformation + National Network, 2011 July (Offsite-box 89, Folder 33)
    - Native Americans/Tribal Youth, 2011 (Offsite-box 89, Folder 34)
    - Title V - State Programs, 2011 (Offsite-box 89, Folder 35)
    - OJJDP/NCCD Curriculum Budget Prep, 2011 (Offsite-box 89, Folder 36)
    - FY2010 Seattle App, 2008-2011 (Offsite-box 89, Folder 37)
    - FY2010 Boston App OJJDP, 2009-2011 (Offsite-box 89, Folder 38)
    - Best Bones Forever, 2009 (Offsite-box 89, Folder 39)
    - Patton Boggs (2 of 4 folders), 2009-2012 (Offsite-box 89, Folder 40-41)
    - Patton Boggs (2 of 4 folders), 2009-2012 (Offsite-box 90, Folder 1-2)
    - NIMHD - Conf Grants (1 of 2), 2011-2012 (Offsite-box 90, Folder 3)
    - NIMHD - Conf Grants. (2 of 2) Digital files, 2011 (Digital folder MS3199, Folder Box90_F3)
      Contains digital files originally stored on CD in Box 90 Folder 3. File formats include Microsoft Word documents and PDFs. Contents of files related to a WSF NIMHD grant and include financial documentation, research strategy and planning, and grant narrative and application.
    - Office of Juvenile Justice and Delinquency Prevention (OJJDP), 2008-2011 (Offsite-box 90, Folder 4)
    - OJJDP - Online Training, 2010 (Offsite-box 90, Folder 5)
    - Americorps, 2011 (Offsite-box 90, Folder 6)
    - Social Innovation Fund, 2009-2011 (Offsite-box 90, Folder 7)
    - PEP/Carol White Physical Ed. Program, ed.gov, 2011 (Offsite-box 90, Folder 8)
    - [DC/ Patton Boggs notes], 2011 (Offsite-box 90, Folder 9)
    - DC trip, 2011 April 19-20 (Offsite-box 90, Folder 10)
    - Website info, 2010-2011 (Offsite-box 90, Folder 11)
  - Subseries IV.B. Advocacy records, 1971-2006; 16 Linear feet in 16 record cartons
    Subseries IV.B contains files related to the gender equity advocacy work of the WSF, particularly the advocacy for Title IX legislation and protections. Documentation of Title IX advocacy includes case files, hearing and testimony transcripts, budget files, position papers, research reports, publications, newsclippings, and correspondence. Case files include those in which WSF's Donna Lopiano served as an expert witness. The files document state and Federal legislation related to gender equity in sport and education over time and research conducted measuring the effects of Title IX and related legislation. The New Agenda conference held in 1983 is also documented. Materials date from 1971-2006.
    The files are arranged in original order, starting with Title IX legislation files removed from hanging folders in WSF office filing cabinets, followed by files removed from storage boxes of the WSF offices.
    - Title IX legislation: Javits Amendment, 1995 (Offsite-box 90, Folder 21)
    - Title IX legislation: Missouri, 1995 (Offsite-box 90, Folder 22)
    - Title IX legislation: Minnesota, undated (Offsite-box 90, Folder 23)
    - Title IX legislation: Illinois, 1995 (Offsite-box 90, Folder 24)
    - Title IX legislation: Washington, 1989 (Offsite-box 90, Folder 25)
    - Title IX legislation: [Congressional testimonies], 1992 (Offsite-box 90, Folder 26)
    - Title IX legislation: Florida, 1984-1991 (Offsite-box 90, Folder 27)
    - Title IX legislation: Michigan Elliott Larsen Civil Rights Act, undated (Offsite-box 90, Folder 28)
    - Title IX legislation: California, 1982-1990 (Offsite-box 90, Folder 29)
    - Gender Equity and the Economics of College Sports by Andrew Zimbalist, 1996 (Offsite-box 90, Folder 30)
    - Title IX budgets: NCAA revenues & expenses manual, 1981-1993 (Offsite-box 90, Folder 31)
    - Title IX budgets, 1980-1991 (Offsite-box 90, Folder 32)
    - Title IX budgets: 1993 graphs NCAA money and participation, 1995 (Offsite-box 90, Folder 33)
    - Title IX budgets: Title IX: The Forgotten Law, Carol J. Miller, 1994 (Offsite-box 90, Folder 34)
    - Title IX hearing, 1989 (Offsite-box 90, Folder 35)
    - Title IX - Cases since 1988 (Civil Rights Restoration Act), 1995 (Offsite-box 90, Folder 36)
    - USOC Constitution and bylaws, 1977-1995 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 1)
    - Title IX Leg. hearings, Congressional letters of support, 1995 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 2)
    - Title IX legislation, 1993 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 3)
    - Amateur Sport Act, Olympic Committee NGB, gender study, 1978-1994 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 4)
    - OCR oversight hearing, 1985-1991 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 5)
    - Title IX Legislation, Administration - Dole Grove City Bill (S.272), 1985 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 6)
    - Title IX: policy interpretation, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 7)
    - Statement of Wendy Hilliard before Subcommittee on Post Secondary Education, Training, Lifelong Learning, 1995 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 8)
    - Testimony before US House of Representatives Subcommittee on Post Secondary Education, Training, and Lifelong Learning - Christine Grant, 1995 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 9)
    - NWLC - Testimony of….before US House of Representatives Subcommittee on Post Secondary Education, Training, and Lifelong Learning, 1995 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 10)
    - Statement of Donna Lopiano before the Subcommittee on Consumer Affairs, Foreign Commerce, and Tourism, 1995 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 11)
    - OCRs letter in re: drill team, 1993 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 12)
    - Title IX: Educational Resource Packet, undated (Offsite-box 91, Folder 13)
    - Participation packet, 1995 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 14)
    - Even with Football, Equity Can Become a Reality Curtis + Grant, U. of Iowa, undated (Offsite-box 91, Folder 15)
    - Title IX's Interest and Ability Issue: The Smokescreen and the Solutions by Donna Lopiano, undated (Offsite-box 91, Folder 16)
    - List of OCR Offices, 1997 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 17)
    - T-9 compliance quiz, undated (Offsite-box 91, Folder 18)
    - Title IX chronology, 1996 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 19)
    - Common questions about Title IX, 1994 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 20)
    - Title IX informational points, undated (Offsite-box 91, Folder 21)
    - Women's Sports Facts - WSF, 1996 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 22)
    - Myth Busting: What Every Female Athlete Should Know, undated (Offsite-box 91, Folder 23)
    - Gender Equity in Athletics/Title IX Educational Fact Sheet, 1995 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 24)
    - Title IX Compliance Quiz - WSE, 1995 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 25)
    - NCAA Gender Equity Study, 1992 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 26)
    - Achieving Gender Equity: Basic Guide to Title IX for Colleges and Universities; by NCAA, 1993 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 27)
    - OCR's Clarification of Intercollegiate Athletics Policy Guidance: 3-part Test, 1980 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 28)
    - OCR compliant forms, 1997 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 29)
    - LPGA statement, 1991 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 30)
    - Significant Events in US Women's Sports History, 1997 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 31)
    - PR - Wendy Hilliard Testifies Before Congress - WSF Speaks Out on Title IX, 1995 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 32)
    - PR - TLPJ - Title IX Lawsuit Against Brown University - Separating Myths from Reality, 1995 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 33)
    - PR - WSF Responds to Brown University's Title IX Decision, 1995 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 34)
    - PR - TLPJ - US District Ct. Rejects Brown University's Title IX Compliance Plan, 1995 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 35)
    - Gender Equity: Judicial Action Related Info, 1996 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 36)
    - Women Intercollegiate Sports, 1994 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 37)
    - NCAA Gender Equity Study, 1997 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 38)
    - Does Football Require Special Relief Under Title IX, 1995 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 39)
    - PR: The Title IX Lawsuit Against Brown: Separating Myths from Reality, 1995 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 40)
    - PR - WSF Responds to American Football Coaches Association Attack on Title IX, 1995 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 46)
    - PR - WSF is Ready for Back to School, 1995 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 47)
    - WSF Position Paper: Addressing the Issue of Drill Team, Cheerleading, Danceline, and Band as Varsity Sports, undated (Offsite-box 91, Folder 48)
    - "More to Cheerleading Than Its Sports Status" - letter to editor, Prince George's Journal, 1995 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 49)
    - Lopiano's FOIA Request re: Title IX Cases, to Norma Canto, 1995 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 7)
    - Penn News - Title IX Complaint Settled by Penn and Women's Law Project, undated (Offsite-box 93, Folder 8)
    - 2, 4, 6, 8… [article], 1995 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 9)
    - Is Cheerleading a Sneaky Way Around T-9, 1995 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 10)
    - Women in Intercollegiate Sport, 1994 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 11)
    - Title IX Legislation 1974 NCAA vs HEW, 1974-1978 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 12)
    - Title IX legislation, 1974 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 13)
    - Title IX Legislation 1973 Policy Int., 1978-1979 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 14)
    - Title IX Legislation, 1979 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 15)
    - Title IX Legislation regulations, 1975 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 16)
    - Title IX Legis. Federal: Amicus Brief Jackson vs Birmingham, 2004 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 17)
    - Title IX Legis. Federal: US Dept. of Ed./Title IX, 1983-2002 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 18)
    - Title IX Legis. Federal: Fair Play Act of 1997 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 19)
    - Title IX Legis. Federal: Gender Equity Study Summary, 1996-1997 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 20)
    - Title IX Legis. Federal: NCAA Gender Equity in Athletics Disclosure Act, 1996-1997 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 21)
    - Title IX Legis. Federal: Title IX Leg. Hearings, 1995 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 22)
    - Title IX Legis. Federal: Title IX Legislation Post. Hearing Action, 1995 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 23)
    - Title IX Legis. Federal: Women in Sport - Collegiate Sports: Administration - Discrimination cases - Mary Hill, 1977-1991 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 24)
    - Title IX Legis. Federal: Title IX Leg. Testimony, 1995 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 25)
    - Title IX Legis. Federal: Title IX Legislation correspondence, 1995 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 26)
    - Title IX Legis. Federal: Title IX Legislation Post Hearing correspondence, 1995 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 27)
    - ASA: Title IX - OCR Clarification, 1996 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 28)
    - ASA: Amateur Sports Act Oversight Hearings, 1995 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 29)
    - T-9 Report - National Coalition for Women and Girls, 1997 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 30)